<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>neildahiya</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/</link><description>Recent content on neildahiya</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 17:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://neildahiya.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Christmas Carol</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/achristmascarol/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/achristmascarol/</guid><description>If I had to describe this book in one word, it&amp;rsquo;ll have to be &amp;ldquo;Beautiful&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Happy&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s so captivating and so well written. It&amp;rsquo;s very different than all of Dicken&amp;rsquo;s works I&amp;rsquo;ve read so far, but a masterpiece indeed. A very short book, but with a great story. It can be read in a couple of hours and if you haven&amp;rsquo;t read something in a while, it&amp;rsquo;s a great one to start again with.</description></item><item><title>Aesthetic</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/photos/moon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/photos/moon/</guid><description/></item><item><title>XXXTentacion album art recreated with my images</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/photos/neiltentacion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/photos/neiltentacion/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Saxophone</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/photos/saxophone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/photos/saxophone/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Great Expectations</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/greatexpectations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/greatexpectations/</guid><description>This was an interesting read. Dickens' books are pretty slow, but the way the story builds up towards the end is just beautiful in all of his books I&amp;rsquo;ve read till now. And this one surely keeps up with the trend. Though some parts of the book were predictable (like the convict&amp;rsquo;s role in Pip falling into fortune), it was still an awesome read.
A bit more happy conclusion towards the end (mostly pertaining to Pip and Estella) would&amp;rsquo;ve been nicer, but nothing wrong with what happened as well.</description></item><item><title>In an Instant - Suzanne Redfearn</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/inaninstant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/inaninstant/</guid><description>This was a good one. It&amp;rsquo;s a quick and really addictive read. I read in a single day. I chose to read this book as I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t find myself reading another page of Pride and Prejudice, and the summary I read of it on Goodreads was really nice.
The overall theme of the book is sad but the ending is really full of redemption. The POV is really unique and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t thought of this before.</description></item><item><title>Pride and Prejudice - Jane Austen</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/prideandprejudice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/prideandprejudice/</guid><description>Read around 70-80 pages and couldn&amp;rsquo;t make myself go through it any longer. The book is so damn slow and boring. Yeah, the title is sort of justified, but not an easy read in any way (IMO).
Rating: NA</description></item><item><title>Vicious - V.E. Schwab</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/vicious/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/vicious/</guid><description>This was a less serious book than the ones I&amp;rsquo;ve read before. I have read several fiction books but none like this (supernatural/fantasy). The best thing about this book was the author&amp;rsquo;s way of writing. It was crystal clear, easy to understand and very unique. The reader got to know about two different times at the same time, alternating every chapter. There was a 12 year gap in every alternate chapter at the beginning and the story in both seemed to lead to the other.</description></item><item><title>Diary of a young girl</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/diaryofayounggirl/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/diaryofayounggirl/</guid><description>This was a special book. It&amp;rsquo;s not really a novel but an actual record of events by a 13 year old girl who ended up being the victim of the holocaust. Should one expect this book to be perfect? Absolutely not, it isn&amp;rsquo;t meant to be perfect. One also can&amp;rsquo;t expect good writing from a 13 year old going through one of the greatest tragedies on the face of the planet.</description></item><item><title>Norwegian Wood - Haruki Murakami</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/norwegianwood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/book-reviews/norwegianwood/</guid><description>The correct way to describe this book would be sad. So many people die. That seems to be the overall theme of the book. I even considered leaving this book half way through but picked it up again because its so beautifully written. It&amp;rsquo;s sad for sure but makes you wanna keep on reading or thinking about what&amp;rsquo;s gonna happen next. Why do most of the books either start or end with a death.</description></item><item><title>Clone</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/photos/neilclone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/photos/neilclone/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Random lines/quotes/lyrics I like</title><link>https://neildahiya.com/lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://neildahiya.com/lines/</guid><description>Mr. Serotonin Man, lend me a gram. You call yourself a friend?
Does your environment affect your thinking or is it the opposite?
It&amp;rsquo;s not magic.
Why not you?
Move out of your comfort zone. You can only grow if you are willing to feel awkward and uncomfortable when you try something new.
If you know what you&amp;rsquo;re worth, then go and get what you&amp;rsquo;re worth.</description></item></channel></rss>